[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
One girl was saved...
The Islander
that we're choosing to keep is...
Carmen.
[narrator] ...but doubt spread.
Bergie is like.
"You're such a strong woman."
The way that situation was handled
is not what I would be looking
for from a partner.
I felt that she was really feeling Bergie.
Be fucking for real.
You can't see through that?
[narrator] Hearts were broken...
Honestly. I feel like we saved the
wrong person. if I'm being blunt with you.
Is it friendship
or is it romantic with us?
It just made me realize
that's gonna my best friend in here.
[sighs]
[narrator] ...and passions reignited.
You wanna kiss me.
Oh. you're dangerous.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Do you mind if I talk to you for a minute?
What you did today hurt me.
It's uncomfortable to watch.
[narrator] And the Hideaway...
"Please pick one couple
to spend the night alone together."
[all] Kay Kay and Keenan!
[narrator] ...opened its doors.
I will see all you guys in the morning.
[narrator] Tonight...
three new bombshells...
We're having a pool party.
[narrator] ...crash the party.
Hi. bitches!
What's up?
-[Destiny] Oh. shit!
-Oh. shit!
[cheering]
Damn!
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
It's nighttime in the villa
and Kay Kay and Keenan
are in the Hideaway.
You can feel the sexual tension
between them.
Sparks are flying. which is not good
'cause that cheap polyester fur
is highly flammable.
-Hold the... No.
-[laughing]
-This is crazy.
-This door is strong as fuck.
-Ah!
-Goddamn. And I'm closing him.
[Keenan] Yeah.
-This is crazy. the whole room is fur.
-Nah.
Nah. this is nice. This is nice.
-[screams]
-Damn. fur everywhere. It's crazy.
Got you a little chocolate.
A little champagne.
You are so pretty.
Thank you.
You need to finish your champagne first
before we out here...
You're nervous! [laughing]
Don't be nervous. it's just me.
[moaning]
[Kay Kay] Where are you going?
[Keenan] You want that glass?
-Here's to us...
-Mmm.
...and a very special connection.
One that's very rare.
One that's swept me off my feet.
Them little things.
Them little old things.
Yeah. one that makes me feel
like a queen every single day.
It makes me feel like I'm worth it all.
Drink the fuck up.
Bottoms up to that shit.
[narrator] After Anna got upset
about Leonardo pawing Kassy.
I said to him.
"Mate. if you can't control yourself.
do what I do."
"Keep those naughty little hands
in your pockets."
[Leonardo] Bro. when I... Sit down.
This is fucking insane.
So. I pull Kassy aside
to go have a kiss over there.
and we're making out. we're kissing.
And as soon as we finish kissing.
who walks by
at the very end. though?
I mean right after sitting
in the same spot.
Anna comes up and she's like...
Tell me how she feels.
I understood. but I just wasn't expecting
to ever talk to her
'cause it didn't seem
like she ever wanted to talk.
Okay.
-So. I was like. "Oh my God."
-So. she saw the kiss?
I don't think she did.
It just felt bad. like. of that time.
I didn't think
she wanted to talk to me at all.
Okay. So. she said all her feelings.
and what did you say?
I just agreed to how she felt.
I understood how she felt.
Like. I'm just in shock of the timing
of how that all went down.
I've never had a timing situation...
Like. that was real bad.
Leo.
So. I didn't give him much room to talk.
I said. "You owe me respect.
and it's not respectful
what you're doing."
Was that bad that I did that?
-No. I'm so proud of you...
-I mean...
What did he say? Give me details!
"I was trying to talk to you about wanting
to give you your distance."
I said.
"I don't care about our conversation."
He's making excuses.
"I care about the way
you're fucking treating me
in front of a group of people."
So. I'm happy you said that. though.
'cause you could just walk around.
act like you don't feel anything
and everything's okay.
but you let him know how you felt.
And I said it makes it so much worse
that it hasn't even been 24 hours.
Okay.
Leo.
your timing period has been terrible.
So bad.
I don't think you've had good timing
since you stepped in this villa.
[Leonardo] Oh. my fucking goodness.
I can't give myself a break.
You cannot give yourself...
You're your own worst enemy in here.
You have been up under one
while completely ignoring the other.
Elaborate.
Leo. you're still in a couple right now.
-She does not want anything to do with me.
-That's not true.
She just wants to know
you still want something to do with her.
You need to pull that girl to the side.
Yeah.
Oh. my God.
Terrible.
Timing.
Oh. yeah.
I said I was gonna talk to you too.
Okay.
So. um...
are you willing to talk to Anna?
Yeah. I am.
Yeah. I just... I'll talk to her.
-Okay.
-I'll talk to her.
Well. y'all talk.
Handle that.
If y'all need to have a talk...
I don't know y'all dynamics
but if there needs to be a talk.
make sure y'all had it. You know?
And that's it.
-Got it. Thank you.
-All right.
Mm-hmm.
Oh. my God. I just feel horrible.
You can't please everybody.
What can you do?
You can't go back in the past.
-Mm-mmm.
-And then. what are we supposed to do?
Tiptoe. then. around everybody?
I don't know.
The timing's just hitting me.
I just wanted to clear it up
in a better way with her. But...
So. the conversation.
it didn't end on a good note?
It didn't end on a great note.
Mmm.
Oh. my God.
Am I a bad person?
No.
I feel like a horrible person.
I don't feel that way only because I know
we're doing what we feel is right.
[Keenan] What is this? Oh. fuck. no.
I'm hiding these.
-[Kay Kay] What is it?
-You're like a little kid.
[Kay Kay] What is it?
-What is it. a nipple clamp?
-Nothing.
-Oh. fuck.
-[laughing]
-Let me see.
-No.
[Kay Kay] You've been bad or good?
I'm always bad. I don't give a fuck.
-Mmm.
-You and that cat...
You and that fucking whip.
and that shit got
hella little strings too.
-You gotta be careful. baby girl.
-Are you scared?
Of you and that whip?
-Uh-uh. don't be scared.
-You're so fine.
-What the fuck can you even do with that?
-I don't know.
You can replace that with these.
[sighs] Fuck it.
Fuck them goddamn nipple clamps.
[narrator]
It's getting hot and steamy tonight.
Keenan's in the Hideaway
having his "way-hay" with Kay Kay.
And Leonardo's getting kissy-kissy
with Kassy-Kassy.
[Carmen] Can you guys not be freaky
while I'm peeing?
I am literally peeing
and can hear you guys.
[Leonardo] I didn't hear shit. bruv.
-[Islander 1] What's all them pillows?
-I took Kay Kay's.
Don't touch my shit.
You guys are making me uncomfortable.
-Bro. I'm right here!
-[Leonardo] Sorry.
What is she doing now?
[Islander 2] She took some of our pillows.
-Oh. good idea.
-She's gonna block the walkway.
[laughing]
[Destiny] That is so funny.
The fort is insane. Touché.
[laughing] That's actually funny. though.
[Kay Kay] Good morning!
-Good morning. goddamn.
-[laughs]
[Anna] Hi. Destiny.
I think they had a great night.
and I hope they got to sleep in.
[Kay Kay] So. how do you feel
waking up in the Hideaway?
I feel like a princess.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I feel good we had some alone time.
I feel like we really needed it.
It was a crazy experience
just to be the first couple in here.
test these springs out.
Bet.
All right. Let's start getting ready.
Pop this real quick.
[Destiny] Don't do me.
[Anna] Does anybody wanna make me eggs?
-Bergie?
-What's up?
-Want me to make you eggs?
-No. I'm just kidding.
I'm not making any more coffee until...
Do you need help with that loofah?
You want me to shave your legs for you.
daddy?
I'm coming!
Don't got to tell me twice.
[narrator] Kassy's pulled Anna for a chat.
'cause right now.
Anna's seriously bugging her.
Detective Anna's not just bugging you.
Kassy.
She's fitted a tracking device
to your car.
So. I first off wanna say...
I am sorry
for that yesterday.
We may have been touchy and stuff.
because we all live together.
And I know that sucks because
if you wanted to
in the outside world. you could have...
-you could block me and Leo.
-Yeah.
-You could be like. "Fuck both of y'all."
And it sucks
that we can't do that in here.
-So. I'm sorry on my part.
-Yeah.
I just want us to be on better terms.
Yeah. no. I appreciate you coming to me.
It was all so soon
to see you guys together.
But I'm happy you woke up realizing.
"Hey. I made this mistake. and I'm sorry."
So. I have a lot of respect
for you for that.
So. yeah.
And. obviously. you knew. like.
I was always saying
if you have a better connection with him.
even if I'm in a couple with him.
get to know him.
And I'm happy that you did.
Just in the future. like.
if this happens with another girl's.
like. couple or whatever...
No. I definitely will talk
to the girl first and I acknowledge that.
And I learned. I feel like
I've learned from this and...
But. like you say.
actions speak louder than words.
So. I have to just do
what I say next time.
I'm happy you guys are reconnecting.
Obviously. it sucks 'cause it's so new.
but at the end of the day.
everything happens for a reason.
I do appreciate you coming to me
and telling me how you feel
and you're sorry and all that.
I really am sorry.
-Can I hug?
-Yeah.
-Can I hug you. please?
-Of course you can.
[squealing]
Finally. a weight has been lifted off
my shoulders.
I mean. I woke up. I just felt completely
guilty of how I acted yesterday.
It's not me.
And so. I'm happy
I got to express how I felt.
and to know that me and Anna
are on good terms.
that's all that matters.
It's like. you guys look good together.
I'm happy for it.
I'm just happy to watch you guys grow.
Hopefully. Leo will do
the same shit with you.
-I'm sorry about that.
-But I do appreciate you.
-I'm glad that you and I are better.
-Yeah. no. we're way better.
[Kassy] Can I hug you?
You know I'm a huggy person.
[squealing]
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Keenan and Kay Kay
are about to leave the Hideaway.
but what did they get up to in there?
Well. a gentleman never tells.
He just acts it out graphically
in a filthy mime.
[Keenan] What's up. lovely Islanders?
Hey!
[shrieking]
Hey. Hey.
[Harrison] Don't be doing that
if you ain't fucking.
We gotta chat first. baby.
-Hey!
-[Anna] Hello!
Kay Kay. we missed you.
-[Anna] You look so beautiful. girl.
-Thank you!
Hey. babies!
-[Leonardo] You cook. my boy.
-My boy.
[Leonardo] How was the night?
Man. if y'all got a little second.
we can slide over to the orange couch.
-Let's do it. I'm down.
-Have a little chat. goddamn.
-[Kay Kay] Let's go to the beach!
-Yes!
-I'll tell y'all.
-[Islander] Okay.
[Hannah] I can tell by the hair
something happened. Shit.
-[Destiny] That makes sense.
-[Hannah] They had a good night!
[laughing]
[Kay Kay] Real good night. honey.
Okay. So. yeah.
I was in the Hideaway last night.
The whole room is fur.
Like. it's white fur.
-[Islander] Oh. my God.
-[Kay Kay] It's real sexy in there. like...
There's a closet with a whole bunch
of freaky shit in there.
-[Kassy] Did y'all use it?
-Yeah.
[cheering]
-[Kay Kay] Yeah!
-That's what we love to hear.
Yes. It was really nice.
We got really close.
we had some good conversations.
some good kisses and stuff.
[Kassy] And stuff?
And stuff?
And stuff. You know.
[Kassy] All right. first base.
second base. third base. home run?
-Home run?
-[screaming]
Sorry. Mommy.
A little excitement over there.
so it has to be good news. baby.
-We heard "home run."
-[Keenan] Yeah.
I was cool. I was comfortable.
We were having
two little glasses of champagne.
a little strawberry.
little chocolate action.
And then they had the little press.
the little mirrored door.
-You open it. hella toys.
-Did you put any toys on?
I ain't gonna lie.
She had me in handcuffs and then...
That's hot. bro.
She was obsessed with the whip.
But other than that. bro. it was fun.
[narrator] After losing Carmen.
poor Dairy Queen
General Manager Bergie's feelings
are as raw as an uncooked patty
and numb as your tongue
after an extra-large Blizzard.
I like your swimsuit.
Thank you. babe. What's going on?
[sighs] I'm feeling destroyed today.
Like. you know.
-Oh. my bubba...
-Yeah.
-Okay. yes. I'm glad you told me.
[Bergie] I was in denial all day.
I wasn't accepting it.
-[Hannah] Yeah.
-And now. I'm accepting it.
I just don't know what else to do.
You know?
I felt. like. since day one.
I was just pursuing Carmen.
Now it's just starting to hit.
I know it hurts in situations like these.
'cause you're like.
"Dang. I really wanted it."
I really wanted it.
I really fought for it.
-Yeah.
-It's just like...
Is someone ever gonna do that for me?
I've had time to process
what happened. and it...
Yeah. I was just in denial yesterday
and now it's finally hitting me.
everything that's happened.
and it's not a fun place to be in.
I felt like I stuck my neck out
on the line
for that whole romantic spark.
and it just dwindled
right in front of my face.
[Hannah] Sometimes.
God puts people in our lives
not for them to change our lives.
but for us to change something
in ourselves.
You learn what you deserve.
-I feel like. in a way...
-Gotcha.
...you are learning your worth.
-So. be picky with your heart...
-Yeah.
...and who you love.
'cause that's what you deserve.
okay?
Yeah. it's tough.
It is tough.
I guess sometimes I just feel like I don't
even get the shot. you know what I mean?
I feel like I'm doing something wrong.
and I just can't see it.
I'm willing to do anything for my person.
It's just I'm hoping someone's willing
to do the same for me.
Maybe it could be a different approach.
"Yeah. I wanna show you
that I care for you and..."
But let them show that too.
Yeah. don't go all in.
Unless you're really feeling it.
Be picky with who you give your energy to.
I am.
I have a lot of love to give. I just need
to find the right person to give it to.
[phone chimes]
-Someone got a text.
-Somebody just got a text.
I got a text!
"Islanders. it's time to dive in as today
you're having a pool party!"
[cheering]
"#Let'sGetWet. #MakeASplash."
[all] Yeah!
[all chanting] Pool party! Pool party!
Yes. pool party! I can't wait!
I'm so excited.
It's giving Miami. it's giving Las Vegas.
It's giving bad bitch.
Pool party!
I love a pool party.
[screams]
We really need this pool party.
Let's have the best time
of our life today.
[cheering]
Pool party!
[Islander] Let's go! We lit!
Cheers to shaking that ass
and making memories that last.
[cheering]
Put it up there. Berg.
-I got it.
-Yeah!
[narrator] Hannah wants to address
a tricky subject beginning with F.
Nope. not Marco's ridiculous fedora.
Feelings.
I've been thinking about
my past stuff a lot. you know?
And I'm very cautious now.
with my heart.
I ignored a lot of things.
things that I should've addressed
in the beginning.
So with you. because I care about you.
I wanna make sure I address
how I'm feeling at all times.
-Okay.
-But you're very receptive too. to...
You know. how I'm feeling.
You don't react bad.
I'm not supposed to. right?
-No. you're not supposed to.
-Okay.
-So that's good.
-Well. you got to tell me.
"Oh. this is good. this is bad."
Okay. I just want you to know we're good.
Yeah. we are good.
I think. when I feel some way.
I have to analyze how I'm feeling.
You get what I'm saying?
Yeah. I don't think I analyze too much.
to be honest.
[Hannah] No. you don't.
But that's you.
and that's okay.
I care about you.
and I'm catching feelings.
Vice versa. Hannah.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
I had a feeling
you were catching feelings.
I feel like things are good.
I'm excited to...
hang out with you every day.
Yeah. me too.
[Hannah] Still feeling good.
I still feel like we're real solid.
He hasn't given me a reason
not to think that.
I don't feel worried
about me and Marco's connection.
-Hey. we both suck. We both suck.
-We suck.
So fuck it.
[laughs]
[narrator] Hello! I think somebody is
about to make a splash at the pool party.
It's a hot new bombshell.
and two security guards who were so fit.
we stuck 'em in shorts
and told them to come along as well.
My name is Kenzo.
I'm 26 years old.
and I'm from Scottsdale. Arizona.
I'm a freelance videographer.
originally from Puerto Vallarta. Mexico.
I look for girls who are very authentic.
who are very confident.
When I see something. I'm gonna go for it.
So I don't care if she's coupled up.
I'm gonna shoot my shot.
I don't remember
the last shot I've missed.
so. I'm gonna keep shooting.
My name is Emily. I'm 25 years old.
and I'm from Houston. Texas. Whoo!
My type is someone funny and silly
and makes me laugh.
I think the girls are gonna be shocked
when I walk in
because I'm tall and tan
and ready to take their man. [laughs]
I'm definitely ready to
piss some people off to get what I want.
My name is Jonah. I'm 24 years old.
and I'm from Shingle Springs. California.
I run my family ranch.
The day starts with feeding the cow.
feed the pig. feed the goats.
I have time for women.
It's all about making time
for things you wanna do.
When I get into the villa.
I'm gonna get to know all the women.
I'm definitely gonna be
like a kid in a candy shop.
I might come out a diabetic.
[Islander] Kay Kay! Kay Kay!
[Hannah] Yes. Kay Kay!
You. Harrison.
Hi. bitches!
-[Carmen] Shut the fuck up.
-What's up?
Oh. shit.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Three new bombshells have arrived.
including two boys.
More competition for Bergie.
And if I know Bergie... and I don't...
He's gonna be absolutely furious.
What's up?
-[Destiny] Oh. shit!
-Oh. shit!
What's going on. everybody?
[Leonardo] Yo. yo. yo!
Bro. what's up?
-You chilling?
-Yeah.
[Leonardo] Shit. I'm chilling. baby.
[screaming]
Three new people just walked in.
Not one. not two. but three hotties.
-What's your name?
-Kassy.
-Nice to meet you. Jonah.
-Nice to meet you.
[Leonardo] These three motherfuckers
come out the water.
This fine-ass girl.
these two dudes who look like
they could cause havoc.
[sighs. chuckles]
Hey. there's your brunette guy.
Yeah. Shit.
The boys are so dreamy.
Oh. my God. I just wanna lick them.
-How are you? Harrison. Good to meet you.
-Emily. Hi. Oh. my God. cute. You too.
Emily's a good-looking girl.
definitely caught my eye.
Red bikini always helps.
a little bit of Baywatch.
I'm definitely not exclusive with Destiny.
I mean. I haven't mentioned commitment
or anything like that.
So. time to shake things up a bit.
This is good. It's good.
-Hi. I'm Carmen.
-Kenzo.
-Nice to meet you.
[giggling]
[laughing]
[Carmen] Oh. my God. I'm so excited.
And I'm excited for them to come in
and do what bombshells do best
and blow shit up.
[Bergie] Welcome to the villa.
[narrator] I said to the Islanders
take bombshells Emily. Kenzo. and Jonah
off and debrief them.
Carmen shouted. "Me first!"
And tried to pull off poor Kenzo's boxers.
-[Islander 1] Okay. tell me everything.
-[Islander 2] Tell us about you.
[Emily] Oh. shit. Yeah. I'm 25.
I'm from Houston. Texas.
[all] Texas!
I'm trying to think what else.
[Kassy] What do you do for living?
-[Anna] Yeah. what do you do?
-I do hair.
I can tell. your hair is fucking stunning.
-[Destiny] What's your type?
-Yeah. the classic question.
I feel like I don't have a type.
You just have to be funny.
You have to be nice.
and you have to be. really silly.
-Yeah.
-[Emily] So. you can look...
Honestly. I kind of like an average
seven out of ten
with a really fucking good personality.
-That's my type.
-That puts them as a ten.
That's real. I like that.
I really am looking for a baby daddy.
-At 25. you start thinking about that.
-[Hannah] Yeah.
I was a slut.
I had my fun time.
and then I've had my relationships.
and then I realized
I'm done wasting time now.
I do really wanna get to know
every guy here.
-[Hannah] Right.
-I'm very open. Like...
I don't like passive-aggressive
and I'm confrontational.
but I try to do it in. like.
-not a bitchy way. but...
-Yeah. Respectful.
[Emily] If I'm feeling something.
I'm gonna tell you.
From the girls in here.
where y'all looking at?
Where are your eyes ranging in?
Then we can kind of give you
some info based upon that.
Open-minded. bro. Honestly. everything.
-Then. shit.
-[Kenzo] Yeah. bro.
I'm excited to talk to every single one.
I'm not really intimidated right now.
I know my cards.
This is the game.
If I have to step on some toes.
may the best man win.
I've dated all types
of different-looking women.
and the one thing that I would say
that is consistent with all of them.
they're all outgoing.
they're super adventurous.
And I also like a woman
that has a flirtatious personality.
[Jonah] I'm ready to shake up the villa.
We are going to have to step on toes
to get to know women.
Bro code on Love Island is no bro code.
I'm just excited to fucking be here.
-[Marco] Yeah.
-For sure.
This doesn't seem real yet.
Can we ask if you have eyes
on any guys in here?
-Keenan is really fucking hot.
-I know.
[Emily] He. in real life.
is someone that I would probably pursue.
-[Carmen] What do you think about Marco?
-Marco.
I think Marco is...
He was my number one for a long time.
-He looks very similar to my ex.
-[Hannah] Really?
So. he's who my eyes go to. kind of.
And also. he seems. like. outgoing.
Which. again.
that's the number one thing for me.
So. off the bat.
I'm definitely interested in him.
How do you guys feel
about the new girl. Emily?
-She's attractive.
-She caught my eye.
I like that sort of body type
and she seemed like
she's a bit. like. out there.
-[Islanders] Yeah.
-And I like that.
Harrison is scarily handsome.
Yeah. he is.
I don't know how anyone's allowed
to look like that.
So. my eyes also go to him.
The girls are so nice.
but at the end of the day.
I have to do what I have to do.
-[Jonah] How are you guys doing?
-[all] Hi.
Kenzo and I would like to come
meet you ladies.
And Emily. if you would like to go
meet the guys.
Oh. my God. I'm nervous!
Fuck!
[Kenzo] Go get 'em.
-[Jonah] Have a good one.
-Thank you. you too.
-How y'all doing?
-How you guys doing?
-[all] Good.
-[Kenzo] Great. This place is sick.
That felt like the longest walk
of my fucking life.
-From one side to the other.
-Hi.
-How are you doing?
-Good. How are you?
-[Keenan] Welcome.
-Do you guys remember my name?
-Emily. right?
-Yeah. I was gonna see who remembered.
-Hi.
-[Leonardo] Nice to meet you.
-[kisses]
Oh. my gosh. The kisses are cute.
-[Bergie] How's it going?
-[Emily] Hi.
-[Leonardo] The besitos is crazy.
-Where am I sitting?
-[Leonardo] Wherever you want.
-Okay. I'll sit right here.
This is nice. I'm not gonna lie.
I kind of like it.
-We wanna know the tea.
-The tea?
[Destiny] No.
you gotta tell us the tea first.
You got to tell us about yourselves first.
[Destiny] Name. age. profession.
dating history. type.
What you're looking for. who you're into.
-Give it to me.
-Okay. So. again. I'm Jonah.
I'm 24. I'm from California.
-Cali.
-[Jonah] Where are you from?
-Palm Springs.
-Okay.
-So I'm up kind of by Tahoe.
I run my family ranch.
I don't necessarily have a type.
I have a personality.
Someone with good teeth.
someone that's outgoing.
someone that you wanna be around.
-[Destiny] Yeah.
-[Hannah] Okay.
Yeah. So. I'm Kenzo.
Originally. I was born in Mexico.
Latino gang!
-You're Latinas?
-[Hannah] Yes.
I'm Mexican and so is Kassy.
-My dad's Mexican and my mom's from Peru.
-Hell yeah.
I was born in Puerto Vallarta.
I moved to the States when I was
ten years old to Scottsdale. Arizona.
I live in Scottsdale. Arizona.
-No way. Yeah.
-[Carmen] You still live there?
[Kenzo] There's no way.
-That's awesome. Yeah. that's cool.
-Okay.
[Kenzo] Very beautiful girls.
but Carmen. Hannah.
those are the two girls
that really stuck out to me.
Um. just... They seem like
very down-to-earth girls.
and I feel very attracted
to those types of girls.
What's your normal type. if you have one?
I really like curly hair.
-[Harrison] Keep that hat on. boy.
-[laughing]
-I just...
-[Leonardo] So where are you from?
Currently live in Houston
for the past couple of years.
Yeah. what about you guys?
[Harrison] I'm from Australia.
-Probably the closest one here. Yeah.
-[Emily] Okay.
I'm from Youngstown. Ohio. but
I currently live in Boca Raton. Florida.
And I'm Italian.
I don't know if you can tell.
That's important.
I'm glad you threw that in there.
Definitely rocking Italian right now.
-What about you?
-I'm Bergie. I'm 23 years old.
I'm a Dairy Queen General Manager.
-I love ice cream.
-Yeah. Me too.
You know. it's the best food in the world.
If I met someone here.
I'd move to where they're at.
-That's like magic to my ears.
-[Bergie] Let's go.
I am so open from this experience.
That's really nice to hear.
'cause that is not a normal thing
to hear from men at all.
Yeah. I'm all in.
Cute.
[narrator] Coming up...
"Smooch the Islander
you wanna be coupled up with."
Oh. shit.
-Bergie.
-Let's go!
Oh. my God.
Damn! Damn!
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
To help the bombshells settle in.
I suggested screening a five-hour
health and safety induction video
hosted by Neil deGrasse Tyson.
but the producers insisted
on playing a daft game.
[Marco] Let's go. guys!
Let's keep this up!
Let's welcome the new guys with a splash.
We're gonna start with my boy Kenzo.
Let's get it!
[narrator] One by one. the Islanders must
dive into the pool and retrieve a dare.
There we go.
They must read out and complete the dare
before the next Islander can dive in.
[Marco] All right. Kenzo.
The question is.
"What's on your sexual bucket list?"
[Kenzo] Um...
Having sex on a Ferris wheel.
[Anna] Ooh! That's kind of romantic.
[narrator] Next up is Emily.
who doesn't want to get her hair wet.
so she's asked Kenzo
to double dip on her behalf.
[Keenan] Nice. Nice. Nice form.
-[Marco] Ten. ten. ten.
-[Keenan] Ten. ten. ten.
Oh. God.
[giggling]
"Smooch the Islander
you wanna be coupled up with."
[screaming]
Oh. shit.
Fuck!
Just do it. Just do it. Just do it.
-Bergie.
-[Bergie] Let's go!
[all cheering]
-[Carmen] Yeah!
-[Keenan] Yeah. Berg.
-[Kassy] Bergie!
-[Keenan] Yeah. Berg!
Oh. wow.
[Emily] My kiss with Bergie
was really good.
I had to test it out to see...
how we are physically and chemistry-wise.
Oh. my God.
Damn! Damn!
[Emily] Was it the best kiss ever?
No. But it was a good kiss.
[Destiny] You go. Bergie.
I thought the kiss was wonderful.
[Bergie] You know what?
I wish it was actually longer.
That looks so fun!
"Islander's choice. Ask a truth
to an Islander of your choice."
-Destiny.
-Yes.
What is the craziest place
that you've had sex?
Mmm.
Don't be shy.
Africa.
Ooh! Okay.
I mean. who says a country. right?
Like. that's...
[laughs]
Skivvies and all.
Oh. my God.
Thank you. Okay. here we go.
"Give a lap dance
to the hottest Islander."
[all] Yeah!
Sit right there.
[Keenan] Wanna put a towel...
Oh. my God.
[laughing. cheering]
[cheering]
[Bergie] I love how he just falls in.
Belly flop.
It's bad?
"Have a three-way kiss
with two Islanders of your choice."
It's me. I know it. [laughing]
Of course I don't wanna share no Harrison.
So. I'm feeling some type of way.
[Harrison] I think it's gotta be between
Destiny and you. right?
I'mma kiss you first. then you kiss her.
-You ready?
-Yes.
-Are you serious?
I wanna kiss you too.
-You wanna kiss me?
-Hell. yeah!
You really think
you a part of this throuple?
-I am!
-[Destiny] Oh. my God!
Come on!
[all] Destiny! Destiny!
I have never kissed
Destiny or Harrison before.
but that was magical.
Can we go again?
Okay. Kenzo. The other two got to kiss
who they wanna kiss.
So you pick the girl you wanna kiss.
Oh. shit.
This is tough.
[all cheering]
I'm very attracted to her.
So. it was a great first kiss.
[Erica] Wow!
I'm happy he kissed me.
because I think he's cute.
-Cannonball!
-[all] Yeah!
Oh. my God.
It says. "Kiss on the cheek the Islander
that gives you the ick."
Um...
I'm sorry. I love you.
[sighs] I did kind of steal her man.
so I definitely am an ick.
-[Destiny] Go. Leo!
-[Keenan] Hey.
-Bro. where does he learn that shit?
-He's a fish. bro.
"Islander's choice. Choose a dare."
You have to kiss
who you would like to be coupled up with.
Well. shit.
Hannah. come here.
[all cheering]
Her lips looked inviting. [laughing]
A small little kiss. But it was good.
I thought it was sweet
that he chose to kiss me.
but because me and Marco
are going so good.
there wasn't a part of me
that wanted to indulge.
Marco was right there.
[all] Yeah!
-That was a fun one.
-Great.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Harrison has a question for Destiny.
"Have you ever kissed a girl?
If so. did you like it?"
-Yeah.
-Really?
-Wait. really? Granted.
-Clearly. I could never say that.
Granted. I mean.
I've never kissed a guy before.
Exactly.
So have you never kissed a girl before?
You know... No.
I have.
Okay. well...
-But that's different.
-That's not that weird.
I guess you didn't tongue...
You may have tongued another girl.
I don't know.
-Is this getting to you? Do you like this?
-This what?
Knowing if I have had
a kiss with another girl.
It's funny.
-'Cause I don't talk about it.
-Yeah.
'Cause I'm interested to find out
how daring and out there you are.
Yeah. you know.
Well. I clearly just did
the little throuple kiss. okay?
-That's for sure.
-Yeah. and?
-[laughing]
-And? And?
You did. you did. you did.
I'm just joking with you.
Thank you for going in for me.
That's all right. Of course.
-Of course.
-I appreciate that.
Think I'm gonna let you get wet?
Except for on me. thanks for that.
[narrator]
Kenzo's pulling Carmen for a chat.
Me and Kenzo have got loads in common.
He's got 0% body fat and spends
90 hours in the gym every week.
I've got 90% body fat and spend zero hours
in the gym every week.
Typically. when you're dating someone.
what qualities do you like in them?
'Cause you said it's all personality.
which I get...
Growing up... I grew up in Mexico.
and so. like. blond. blue eyes
is like not very common there.
So. when I moved to the States.
I was like. "Fuck. this is so hot."
And so. at a young age.
I was just really into blond. blue eyes.
I always say I like blonds
and. like. light features.
but all of my ex-boyfriends
are brunette with brown eyes.
So. it doesn't actually matter.
It's kind of like you said.
I'm a big personality person.
Confidence is big for me.
I don't know
if you're a family person or not.
but I'm huge with my family.
-Yeah?
-My family is everything to me.
I'd rather stick with my family
than to go out.
So. that's honestly
one of the big things I look for.
So. I grew up in Wisconsin and my mom
and dad and brother are still there.
-Mm-hmm.
-And when I go home to Wisconsin.
I do not leave my mom's side.
We are tied at the hip.
Even though it sucks leaving family.
it makes you love them even more.
Distance makes the heart grow fonder.
Yeah. You really learn to appreciate them
and everything.
Yeah. no. I love that.
I am honored that Kenzo kissed me
and came and pulled me for his first chat.
That's definitely a good feeling
and a good sign.
I've been saying
I want someone to come in here
and be about me.
and he's giving me that energy.
And it seems like we do...
We would be each other's types.
What's your game plan?
I've had such a good time
in the last five hours I've been here. so...
-Yeah.
-We're all here to experiment. you know?
And try different things.
I'm gonna keep doing that.
[Carmen] How are you feeling?
Who are you feeling?
Obviously. I kissed Bergie.
He just has all my... What I'm looking for.
-Yeah.
-He's not afraid of commitment.
-That's what I want. you know?
That's clear. and you kind of
have to feel that out with everyone else.
But with that being said.
when I picked him. I kind of was like.
"Maybe that wasn't a good choice."
Because I think he goes fully in.
-Yeah. So now...
-And I was...
That's not your fault.
Maybe just make that clear
in your first chat.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-How open you are.
But...
Damn. Marco is so fucking cute.
-[Anna] Talk to him.
-Go pull him for a chat.
-[Carmen] Yeah.
-[Anna] Do it.
Start your Love Island experience now.
We'll be watching. We'll be like...
-Yeah.
-Yeah. okay.
[Anna] You got this. queen.
-[Emily] Hey. Marco.
-[Marco] Hey.
-Would you like to have a chat with me?
-I would.
Let's go. Let's go in that cute little...
-The little...
-"Breathe."
Breathe? Yeah.
[Emily] I know you're pretty... I don't
know if "serious" is the right word.
-Yeah. no.
-But. like...
I just kind of wanted to get
to know you first just because...
Ask some questions.
-Like I said. you're new. so...
-I know...
-[Marco] I'll just...
-But I don't even know what to ask.
I guess a question I could ask you is
what are you looking for?
-I'm looking for my baby daddy.
-Okay.
Like. I have had my fun.
and I've been in
two long-term relationships.
and it just obviously didn't work out.
But I don't wanna like...
-rush anything. 'cause it's so important.
-Gotcha.
So I'm trying to find someone
who's like my best friend.
who I'm gonna have fun with every day.
and someone who's just looking
for the exact same thing as me.
And can see himself being a loving father.
-Yes.
-Okay. I appreciate that.
I'm not even gonna waste my time
with people that don't look
or aren't looking for that too. you know?
I 100% agree.
And that's kind of where I sit.
Now. when I went into my mature life.
I realized I wanna find a girl who's gonna
be a loving mother that I wish I had.
-Yeah.
-I think we have that in common.
-I'm a family guy.
-Same.
I really wanna have as many kids
as God blesses me with.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
[Emily] Off the bat.
Marco has definitely caught my attention.
I just think he's really cute.
I think. outside the villa.
looks-wise. he's the one person
I would definitely go for.
Like I said. I'm glad that you said
that you're attracted to me.
-I am.
-That you wanted to get to know me.
Yeah. You just definitely caught my eye.
Yeah?
Fuck.
Yeah. when Emily came in
and expressed that I was her type.
obviously. it's a good feeling knowing
that a girl is interested in me.
It's never a bad feeling in that sense.
I know Hannah's kind of on the edge.
It's gotta be a little tough.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Anna was headed to the day bed
with photographer Kenzo.
Last time I lounged on a day bed
near a photographer.
I was the cover star
of Sports Illustrated's Swimsuit Issue.
Pale Scotsman Edition.
-[Anna] How are you feeling?
-I'm feeling good.
Have you had a good experience
in here so far?
Yeah. I haven't found my person yet.
but I've learned things about myself.
how to deal with problems.
Did you end things with Leo?
-I ended things with him last night.
-Do you have your eyes on anyone?
Like...
-Maybe.
-Like...
-Kenzo and Anna are having a pretty convo.
-[Hannah] Yay.
-Okay.
-I love that for Anna.
Yeah.
[Kay Kay] He talked to Carmen already.
[Hannah. Destiny] Okay.
He likes blonds with blue eyes.
That's his type. He said that?
Uh-huh. That's what Marco said.
[Hannah] He's a good-looking boy.
She was nervous. I was like. "Girl.
just go be your hot self."
Okay?
Obviously. I wanna find my person.
but I don't force things.
-Yeah.
-Like. I don't...
I'm not a pushy person.
I'm very go-with-the-flow
when it comes to that.
That's good. I like that.
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
-Love this for Anna.
-Yeah.
So my chat with Anna is very chill.
It was very peaceful.
I felt really good vibes.
I'm gonna keep trying to see if I can
build a deeper connection with Anna.
-I love going to the gym.
-Yeah. yeah.
I'm like. "Well. I like to work out."
-Yeah?
-I'm like. "Me too."
Have you been working out here?
Honestly. no.
-[Carmen] I'm coming by you guys.
-[Leonardo] Yes. you are.
[narrator] Carmen enjoyed her chat
with photographer Kenzo.
although she was surprised
when he flashed her.
She thought there was more than enough
natural daylight for a good picture.
So talk to us. baby.
What happened over there?
How was the conversation?
[Carmen] It was good.
-Yeah.
-No. it had to have been.
No. it was just very much like...
Getting to know you.
Yeah. it wasn't anything intense.
It was very quick chat.
-[Leonardo] Mm-mmm.
-But it was good.
I'm out and I'm looking at guys.
blond hair and blue eyes.
Like. I would approach Jonah.
But all the guys I end up dating
look like Kenzo. 'Cause it's personality
for me and I've always said that.
-[Kay Kay] At least you got both options.
-I always thought you'd go for Harrison.
[Carmen] He's just too intense.
-He just doesn't really flirt with me.
-Flirt too much.
He doesn't do fun things.
He seems closed off.
With me. he's one of my favorite people
in here right now.
-Is this your hand?
-[Carmen] I'm holding her hand.
-I was like. how did...
-He was holding my hand holding your hand.
-Which is so fitting.
-[Kassy] We're done.
-We're fucking done.
-Which is so fitting for us.
I'm just curious what they talked about.
-She seems cool.
-[Destiny] She seems...
Destiny. "She seems..."
Who just doesn't give a fuck.
[Emily] Can I join you. guys?
-[Leonardo] Yeah. come through.
-Yeah. of course.
Welcome. We're just shooting the shit.
How were your chats. though?
I had one with Marco.
-[Kassy] How was that?
-I love him.
-Oh. fuck.
-He's just so perfect.
-It's annoying.
-Oh. my God.
-[Hannah] Happy to antic.
-Yeah.
Low-key. she gives that vibes to me.
I'm sure she could be a cool girl.
but she seems like she don't give a fuck.
If I'm being real.
She did come in here
and say exactly what the fuck she felt.
She did. she did. No. for real.
I just feel like a bitch.
-The whole time. I'm like. "I'm a bitch."
-[Carmen] Girl. no.
-I know. This is just weird.
-We're all in here to get to know...
[Leonardo]
You're just having your conversation.
Don't worry what other people
are telling you.
Just do what you want.
'cause you're here for yourself.
[Emily] Yeah. I know.
I have my eye on Marco.
We had a chat and I definitely like
what I did learn about him.
And he's just super fucking cute.
so I am prepared to shake things up.
[narrator] Next time...
old tensions heat up.
Had you been making out with Leo?
He kissed me yesterday.
Just to hear that.
it's another jab to the heart.
What the fuck?
This isn't me.
[narrator] And the bombshells...
get to work.
I'm feeling it. I wasn't sure.
Every single guy
that I finally start to like.
they always pick someone
who's more fun. more bubbly.
He's a piece of shit
if he's gonna say that.
He's a piece of fucking shit
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm